[
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Yesterday, I ____ to the park.",
      "answers": ["went", "go", "going"],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "My sister ____ a delicious cake last night.",
      "answers": ["baking", "bake", "baked"],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "The dog ____ after the ball in the garden.",
      "answers": ["chase", "chased", "chasing"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "We ____ a movie at the cinema on Friday.",
      "answers": ["watch", "watched", "watching"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "They ____ breakfast early this morning.",
      "answers": ["had", "have", "having"],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "She ____ a new dress for the party.",
      "answers": ["buying", "buy", "bought"],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "I ____ my homework before dinner.",
      "answers": ["do", "did", "doing"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "The plane ____ at 10 pm last night.",
      "answers": ["took off", "take off", "taking off"],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "They ____ in the pool all afternoon.",
      "answers": ["swim", "swam", "swimming"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "He ____ a cold last week.",
      "answers": ["having", "have", "had"],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "We ____ pizza for lunch yesterday.",
      "answers": ["eating", "eat", "ate"],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "She ____ a song on the guitar.",
      "answers": ["playing", "played", "play"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "They ____ to bed early last night.",
      "answers": ["went", "go", "going"],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "He ____ her a beautiful flower.",
      "answers": ["give", "gave", "giving"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "The thief was ____ in the act.",
      "answers": ["catched", "caught", "catching"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "We ____ to the park yesterday.",
      "answers": ["go", "went", "gone"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "The baby ____ all night.",
      "answers": ["cries", "crying", "cried"],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "He ____ me a letter a while ago.",
      "answers": ["send", "sending", "sent"],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "The spider ____ her finger.",
      "answers": ["bites", "bit", "bitten"],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "She ____ the writings on the board.",
      "answers": ["erase", "erased", "erasing"],
      "correct": 1
    }
]
